≠Parisa Javidfar | Frontend Engineer

Tehran, Iran | Linkedin | Gmail | +98 09372092056

Professional summary:

Talented and results-driven frontend engineer with over 4 years of professional experience. I have developed a deep understanding of modern frontend frameworks and a passion for taking on new challenges, solving problems and sharing my knowledge with others.

Work Experience:

Frontend Engineer, Soshyant Financial Tech Company (Farabi Brokerage)

Oct 2021 - Present

- Developed a mono-repo Farabi Mobile application and Farabi's website By using common core modules between the mobile app and the web, which increased the speed of development and the integration of the project, built on Vue and typescript.
- Developed a mono-repo design system using Vue and tailwind, Creating advanced, accessible components with a mobile-first approach. Contributed initial codebase and successfully released the project as an NPM package and typescript.
- Collaborated with chapter members sharing knowledge.
- Collaborate with other developers engaging in continuous code reviews and pair programming to ensure top-notch code quality and adherence to best practices.
- Enhance workflow using JIRA and Gitlab integrations. Streamlined the development process

Frontend developer, Arvanik (Sarafi bahmani)

Mar 2021 - Oct 2021

- Developing and refactoring of financial and accounting systems, built on Vue and quasar.
 Contributing to a dynamic scrum team, implementing agile methodologies and utilising innovative tools like Azure.
- Migrated financial system stores from Vuex to Pinia, ensuring consistency, maintainability, and reduced bundle size.
- collaborating with designers to implement user-friendly components that seamlessly integrate with diverse themes, locales, and time zones.

Frontend developer, Akam Khodro Vira

Jul 2019 - Oct 2020

- Developing B2B and B2C panels , built on Vue and Vuetify.
- Developed custom, modular, and reusable components to enhance the efficiency and consistency of the development process.

Frontend developer , khorshad health

Sep 2018 - Jul 2019

- Development and refactoring of the firm CRM system and also admin panel, built on Angular-is and Material.
- Refactored codebase with the aim of improving performance and increasing reliability.
- Support of mobile applications of the corporation built on ionic.

- Development and development of mass sale systems and ERP, built on JQuery and Bootstrap.
- working closely with back-end developers and designers to deliver cohesive web applications.

Skills:

Programming: (JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML5, CSS/SASS/LESS),

Version control: (Git, GitLab, GitHub),

Frameworks and libraries: (Vue3, Vue2, Qusar, Vuetify, Vue CLI, Tailwind, Vue test),

Methodologies: (Agile, Scrum, Kanban),

Socket: (Socket IO)

Soft skill: (Teamwork, Problem-solving, Fast-learning, Mentoring),

Miscellaneous: (UI/UX, CI/CD, DOM, Webpack, Vite, PWA, Responsive design)

Education:

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology (IT)

2011 - 2014